

# LISANDRO BIGI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

Hello! My name is Lisandro Bigi. I'm from Córdoba, Argentina, and I'm a Front End Developer and an Anthropologist. I have knowledge and experience in: React | Vue.js | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | TypeScript | Git | Wordpress. Also I have an advanced English level.

I'm interested in Web Development, Responsive or Adaptive Web Design, User Interfaces (UI), User Experience (UX), Front-end, Web3 and Web Design.

# CONTACT

+54 9 351 631 9690



bigilisandro@gmail.com



Córdoba, Argentina

## SKILLS



React













## EXPERIENCE

**INCLUIT**, React Developer

JUN 2022 - PRESENT

Currently working for iDocket company in the development of a UCMS software platform. Using ReactJS for the front-end development.

PENGYI LABS, Front-end Developer

JUN 2020 - JUL 2022

I worked as a Front-end developer for a software company with projects in Vue and React for clients all around the world.

**KICKSTA**, Front-end Developer

OCT 2020 - NOV 2021

I worked for this US company in their own main product Kicksta and in their others web applications such as InfluenceGrid and Wedding Hashers.

#### EDUCATION

**EDUCATIONIT**, Blockchain Ethereum Solidity

MAY 2022 - AGO 2022

**CODERHOUSE**, React.is

FEB 2020 - JUN 2020

**ACAMICA**, Full Stack Web Development

NOV 2019 - JUN 2020

**CODERHOUSE**, UX/UI Design

MAY 2020 - SEP 2020

FFyH - UNC, Anthropology Degree

FEB 2013 - MAR 2020

**CODERHOUSE**. Web Designer

OCT 2019 - DIC 2019



